BGM
BGM BGM
BGMBGMよっしゃーにがいいですかミルクティー お水お茶
No, water, water, ok, let's have some water, eat some sweets, ok, ok.
I love it!
I feel like a café waitress... sorry I spilled it...
Sorry, I spilled it.
Don't spill it!
Sorry.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
I'll drink to that.
Oh, my God, it's spilling a lot.
It's spilling a lot.
It's okay.
Okay. - Cheers.
Cheers.
Water.
Water. Yes, sir.
Well, if you're here to have a snack like this... Yes, what is it? What do we do? What do we do? Sleep? Sleep?
I got you some water, but you have to do it like this.
I can sleep like this.
Why don't we do it sometimes? On the couch.
Like this.
Boom.
When you wake up early.
I can't get up.
You're gonna hurt your back.
Was there ever a time when you had a really bad back?
Why don't you sleep normally?
I'd sleep on the floor.
And then I'd wake up and go to work.
And then I'd wake up and I'd go to work, and I'd feel like I was in bad shape.
I was sleeping on the floor.
Well, I'm not sleeping here anymore. I'm going to hurt my back.
I'm sorry.
So...
Do you want to see something?
Sure.
Let's watch Netflix.
I love Netflix.
I don't think there's a lot of people here who watch it.
I think I'm the one who watches a lot of it.
What do you have? Anything recent you'd recommend?
Can I start on the high road?
Yes, you can.
Speaking of Netflix.
Stranger Things.
You've heard of it? I have. I've never seen it.
Yeah, I think a lot of people have.
You know, you open up Netflix, and it's always on there as a recommendation or something.
It's about a fictional small town called Hawkins.
It's a very peaceful town where there's no crime.
And one of the four boys who live there goes missing.
So the other three go looking for him, and they meet a girl with a psychic gift, and they join her, and the four of them go looking for him, and that's pretty much how it goes in season one.
And they're looking for the boy, and they're looking for him.
The sound of the music is really good, and it's very attractive.
Even in very serious scenes, there's a lot of that music playing.
I was also very moved by that, and there was one scene that I really liked.
The four boys were bullied a little bit, and they found the body of a missing boy.
The body of the missing boy is found.
And they say he's dead, in the city.
And then there's a very sad incident at school.
You know, like a school assembly.
And then the bullies who were picking on them, like that guy, died.
You know, people died, and you say things like that.
And I get a little mad, and I push him away.
And then, you know, there's this girl over here with super powers.
And I'm like, “You know what?
And then I make her shit her pants about the bully.
And the girl with psychic powers has a habit of getting nosebleeds when she uses her psychic powers.
And, you know, she's got this side of her mind...
You know, like, “Suck it up.
There's a scene where she wipes the nosebleed.
I like that scene the best in the world, and I rewatched it many times.
You know, I just love it so much that I watch it over and over again.
Yes, well, I mean, I like that part a lot, but it's comical, it's sci-fi, it's got a horror element to it.
It's comical, it's sci-fi, it's got horror elements.
It's a work with a lot of elements.
It's a work with a lot of errors in it.
And as the season goes on, they become more mature.
And then there's a little bit of adolescent trouble, and then there's a little bit of adolescent trouble, and then there's a little bit of complicated feelings that kids go through at that age.
It's very skillful. It's very interesting.
You are very lively when you talk.
Yes, it is. It's so interesting.
You don't get a chance to talk like this very often.
I'm sometimes asked if I have a favorite work.
But Satsuki is Satsuki's
I...
Well, first of all, speaking of Netflix...
Well, first of all...
That kind of thing...
How do I get into the Itaewon class?
I haven't seen it.
So why haven't you seen it?
I was in the Corona disaster when it first hit, so I didn't see it, so why haven't you seen it? Hey, I...
I was in the Corona disaster when it was popular.
I haven't seen it.
Have you seen Love's Emergency Landing, by the way?
You haven't?
I don't really watch dramas.
Oh, you mean like that?
I'm just like, “Oh, that's what it's about.” And I'm always nervous.
I see.
I can't watch them when they're popular.
I'm such a jerk.
What about Itheon?
I don't know about Itheon.
I like Candra a lot.
In many ways.
I mean, it's a very unique genre.
In my opinion.
I've always loved romances and stuff like that.
I don't know, I really like Candra.
It's really, really great. It pulls you right to the heart of the matter.
And then, at the end, it's like...
I don't know why it often ends with a big explosion at the end, but do you have that image of Korean movies?
I'm not used to being on the edge of my seat in a movie like this.
It's quite long, but seriously, I finished it in two days.
I finished it in two days.
Do you like that kind of thriller? Do you like thrillers?
I love it! I love it! I love to watch it.
I love it when it's really refreshing, and I love it when it's really refreshing, and I love it when it's really refreshing, and I love it when it's really refreshing, and I love it when it's really refreshing, and I love it when it's really refreshing.
I have that burning feeling in my heart.
It's been there for a long time.
I have a long period of frustration.
I don't know why.
This is the kind of frustration that made me like this work so much.
Oh, my God!
Each one of them has a story to tell.
I see.
Axojim, right?
So, I mean...
I can't stop wondering why.
I already have a favorite movie.
Can you tell me what it's called?
“Beneath the Surface of the Seine.
It's a French shark movie.
It's the kind of movie you think of when you think of shark movies.
This is a great movie.
I mean, shark movies nowadays are more about how to make a shark look scary.
I mean, shark movies these days are all about how to make sharks look scary.
I don't know how to say it.
There's a lot of competition.
For example, they've added three heads, or six heads, or more heads.
Or making a shark that flops around on the ground.
What head?
A shark with six heads.
I made a shark with six heads...
The shark movie industry is all about how bad you can make a shark.
The shark movie industry was competing with each other.
Then along came this assassin, under the surface of the Seine River.
It's a strong shark, but it's big, and it's got a lot of freshwater...
Sojuerga Research.
It can survive in freshwater, and it's also a little bit more fertile, but...
But their basic specs are the same as sharks... and they have been introduced into the river... the Seine... in France.
And when a triathlon is held in the Seine, everyone swims in the river, and a shark comes into the river, and there's a big panic.
It's already a big panic, but it's a movie where they do everything they shouldn't do.
But then there's the incompetent mayor who notices the shark, and the shark oceanographer says, “This is a bad idea, this is no time for a triathlon,” and he says, “If we do it here, people will die.
You have no idea how much money we're spending to hold this event here.
There are incompetent mayors who don't listen to the economic effect of the event.
This is the royal road.
This is a movie that goes on and on forever.
That's what this movie is about.
It's a movie that's been getting a lot of attention recently from people who like shark movies.
It's kind of in the description section.
It's a shark movie that's a little bit B-movie.
It's different from that.
Chaymus
Charmouth Jaws or Deep Blue.
It's a good film that ranks up there with the best of both shark movies.
It's in the top 10 in 93 countries in its first week of distribution.
The thing that's great about it is that it has a really great ending.
The triathlon really takes place, and then the sharks come.
At that point, I thought, “This is going to end with Senegal turning red.
I thought, “Oh my God!
The last part is even better!
You know what?
I can't even imagine.
Oh, I remember you saying something like that...
I don't know.
Outrageous.
Yes, sir.
It's going to end up like that.
It's going to be a festival!
In addition to the festive ending, the ending is the best ending ever!
If you're new to shark movies, or if you're new to shark movies, this is the movie for you!
You really are a shark movie teacher, aren't you? No, no, no, I'm fine with that.
I've probably seen more of those panic horror movies than most people.
I think I've seen more than most people.
I don't know.
I've seen so much of that stuff.
I've seen them all.
Recently...
Netphys, you know, like the 72 species of dangerous creatures
Like those 72 dangerous species that live in Latin America.
They do exist.
It's a documentary about 72 dangerous creatures that live in Latin America.
Oh, my God, wait, that scared the shit out of me.
I mean, if you don't like it, you don't like it, and I guess I couldn't get enough of that movie, and now I'm watching documentaries about real people.
Oh, it's a documentary?
Yes, it is.
Wow, that's amazing!
I guess there are a lot of people who don't like it.
It's like a cloud.
Clouds, not like snakes or crocodiles.
Leopard seals.
Yes, yes, yes, leopard seals, yes, yes, yes.
Lenki eel is so bad!
I'm kind of addicted to them.
Homomorix spider snakes
Rattlesnakes
Black widow spider
Yes, yes, yes
The camaraderie of the camaraderie demo is amazing!
Oh, my God, they're doing it piece by piece.
Oh, yeah?
Yes, actually.
I can't help but look at that.
I'm afraid I've said too much about my prejudices. Tell us your prejudices.
I only watch romance.
I wonder... but there's an app called Love Alarm that helps you fall in love.
I've never heard of it.
It's an app on your phone.
If someone likes you within a 10-meter radius, this alarm goes off.
What's that?
It's an app that goes viral.
This app is going viral.
Everyone at school has it.
And it's a boy who's the main character, and his love alarm goes off all the time... in all kinds of places.
I love the way she and Jojo fall in love, and I love the way she smiles at him.
If it's a story about two cute, doggy-like high schoolers who are madly in love with each other, will the alarm go off when they fall for each other? It's not like it's the first time they've met.
It starts with a kiss.
Why?
Why is that?
I don't know how it starts.
And then the alarm goes off, and it's just the two of them.
Sono and Julia.
But Sono has a best friend, a best friend who's been around forever, so there are two alarms after all. Sono and Jojo, you know. But there's Sono's best friend, his best friend who's been around forever.
What's his name? That one? That's a position like Rui Hanazawa in Hanayama.
I have a best friend named Haeyeon. We are good friends here.
Haeyeon also falls in love with Jojo, and it's a love triangle, a love triangle omaga.
But that's all I'm going to say.
I know how they feel about each other.
You'd think it would work out.
But it doesn't.
There are a lot of idiots who do that.
The way the first season ended...
The way it ended in season one...
I thought it should end happily, but I guess a happy ending isn't the norm.
I think it's not a given that they're going to end happily ever after. It's back!
You know, you know...
You know...
I like it. It's a nice tease.
I like that tease, too...
You can enjoy both of them.
And you can enjoy Haeyeon, too.
Oh, so she's a fan of either one or the other.
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
You know, you're either a Rui Hanazawa fan or a Rui Hanazawa fan.
Or, you know, the Dou Akira group.
I'll use a Japanese analogy.
If you want to get a pure “kyu-kyu” feeling, watch it. It's a high school student's theory.
Recently, I've been getting into genres that I hadn't seen before, even if they're not romances.
That's why I think I'll give it a try.
It's really fun!
I love it.
So... can we talk about one more Henshin Love movie?
Here you go.
There's a movie called “The Village Hunt”.
It's a French film.
Horror?
Panic horror.
It's about a farmer.
Do you know what an inago is? Like crickets.
There are rice paddy farmers.
Yeah, I thought so too.
But they're having a bad harvest.
I mean, they're skinny.
If they don't grow well, they don't taste good at all.
And I was wondering what to do.
And then, by some chance, the locusts started feeding on the blood of living creatures.
And then, in no time at all, they grew up to be so delicious.
And then the locusts think, “Oh, shit, I'm so sorry.
And then the locusts start feeding on their own blood.
And then they multiply like crazy.
They get really fat.
And at the same time, they go berserk.
And then they got out of control.
But you know what?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
This is good.
It's like, “I'm in over my head.
The main character is running around trying to do something about it.
And then, you know, when he comes back home after going out...
I was raising rice in a plastic greenhouse.
And the plastic of the greenhouse breaks through the vinyl.
It comes out like a tornado from Inako's body.
It's like a big tornado of rice plants.
It's like a tornado in the sky.
What am I going to do now? I'll never forget that scene.
I'll never forget it.
It's the end of the world.
I can't recommend it to anyone, to be honest.
I mean, if it was a shark movie like this... but an insect movie... you have to choose the right person...
I can't help but recommend it to that person.
Algorithms are great!
It's great!
I really don't think you need to see this one, to be honest.
It's just that when a film like this is on Netflix...
That's what I want to...
I want to tell you that I think it's great.
Because if I didn't know it was there, I wouldn't have seen it.
I wouldn't have seen it.
2021. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't think you're interested in that at all.
I'm not really into that kind of thing, but my mom is watching Alice in Wonderland right now, so...
I see.
My mom and I are both into that kind of thing.
I haven't finished the latest episode yet, but I've seen it.
I've seen it, but I haven't finished the latest episode yet... it's more like Al's genre... or if you want to put it in a genre... death games... they try to kill people in the best way possible... other movies are more like that...
Oh, I see... I see... I can't stand to watch it.
I can't stand to watch it.
But I thought this film was made in a way that was easy to watch.
There's a scene where a guy has a bomb around his neck and it explodes.
If it was overseas, the head would be removed.
I think they show the head coming off and even the part where the head is coming off.
If it was a death game film...
But in this one, the head is not removed.
I was quite surprised that the head wasn't removed.
I heard that there are death games that don't remove the head.
I remember thinking, “Hmmm...” when I was a kid.
Look at the country now.
I think it's common for people to say, “Let's blow it up!
I can't get fired.
I think it's just a certain point of view.
In other films, I'm sure you can do it.
I think that's the charm of this work.
I think it's quite good.
I imagine it was rather popular.
Yes, it was very popular.
This is probably the first time I've seen it done properly.
I mean, it's a wrestling game in that genre.
I mean, it's the first time I've really stepped into that genre.
I've stepped into it.
The image is easy to see.
Even if you're a beginner
I think it's relatively easy to see, even for beginners.
But you know what?
The first one
It's just what I think.
It's not at all what I think it is.
In the very beginning, there is a space between the squares.
and then
There's a way to get out of it.
That's...
There's a movie called “Cube”.
I wondered if it was an homage to that movie.
So I was thinking that people who have seen a lot of movies like that might also enjoy it.
I was thinking, “Isn't this like this? or something like that.
I thought, “Yes, I feel something like that work.
I'm sure there are some thoughts from the people who are talking in this order.
That's why I tend to look at the king.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was just talking about love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love.
Well, there's a work called “Even though I know...
I've never heard of it before.
It's called “Kuri2”... what year is it?
It's quite popular among young people.
It's very popular among young people. It's 2021.
It was popular a while ago.
It's a type of relationship between a man and a woman who want to be more than friends and less than lovers.
Girls who maybe don't believe in love, but want to be in love.
They don't want to be in love, but they don't want to be in love.
I've got a girl who wants to be in love.
But she's really a terrible person.
A boy.
What do you mean? Good? Bad?
Hard to say.
I don't know, maybe he's not so bad at all.
He's the type of girl who plays with girls.
Takiyon is... but this girl, Navi... you know, you're not supposed to like her... but you do.
But I can't help but like her even though I know that.
I see... so that's what you mean when you say “even though you know it.
There are a lot of connotations in the title, even if you know that.
This... is not a heart throb.
My heart aches.
No, it's too much excitement.
No, it's too much, it's too much, it's too much, it's too much.
No, no, no, wait a minute... and then I'll look at it and then I'll close the screen and then I'll look at it again like this... and then I'll look at it again like that.
I'm playing with him, but in the end, he's still devoted to Navi. Oh, at first it was just for fun, but....
But they're not honest with each other.
But neither of them are honest.
It's frustrating.
Yes, it is.
Outrageously.
Yes.
That's also good.
Heh.
They're both not very honest, and there's a story behind their clumsiness.
There are a lot of heartbreaking scenes.
And this one, too.
It was a little bit of an adult layered pattern.
Because they're college students.
It's different from the high school students' story.
The story of the college students is going on.
The fashion of Navi in the first place.
That's another aspect of the story.
She's so cute.
I admire her clothes and make-up.
I'd like to take some of their fashion into my own.
I think the girls would love it, and I think they'd be happy with the way I make it.
I think it's great that you're so close, not only to the work, but also behind the scenes.
So, I can't stop looking at the work, looking at the making of the work, and then going back to the work again. I know, it sounds really interesting, but...
But it's just an hour long story.
I really can't stop once I've seen it.
I really didn't sleep well the whole time I was watching this.
I'd like to see it again.
I can watch it over and over again and still enjoy it.
I'll check it out.
There's a Korean movie that I saw recently.
It's called The Call.
It's a Korean horror suspense film.
It's kind of a psychological thriller.
Psycho-thriller kind of movie.
This one.
This is the first time I've seen a Korean movie
It's true.
I'm not saying I know how to do this, but...
I'm used to watching Korean movies.
I've seen it done in movies.
Like “Otoke”.
OTOKE OTOKE
I didn't know there was such a thing.
This is really interesting.
One day I got a phone call... and when I picked it up...
And I hear a voice asking for help.
And I ask, “Who are you? I ask.
And I'm like, “Who are you?” but I can't get through to him.
And I'm like, “What's going on?
So I'm doing some research, and it turns out...
It's like the phone is connected to that place from years ago.
I'm not connecting the place, I'm connecting the time, and the phone is connected.
And the person that the phone is connected to, the mother is some kind of exorcist.
And it connects to a girl who's being abused.
And she's asking for help every day, and I can't do anything about it.
But we can't do anything about it.
So I try to do something about it.
And then I found out that the girl was killed by the exorcist's mother.
And I tried to stop it somehow.
And I'm going to save her.
And that's the future.
So the story of if is going to go on and on and on.
The story of the ifs is going to go on and on and on.
It's pretty interesting.
And the other actor's performance was really good.
I don't know...
He's playing the role of a psychopath.
A psychopath.
But you know what?
He's got this great posing.
Like how he smokes cigarettes.
That's the kind of thing that stuck with me.
I've never really seen Korean horror films.
I'd never seen much of it.
I thought it was really interesting.
After that, I started watching a lot of Korean films.
I have the image of going to a pretty deep level.
I didn't know they were going to go that far.
Scary situations, for example.
You know, Satchan...
There are a lot of big twists and turns in his works.
There are a lot of big twists and turns in that film.
I thought it was a Korean movie in the sense that it was a Korean movie.
I was just looking at the cast of the movie.
I saw Mr. Taxi.
If you like Korean movies, it might be good if it's a Korean movie.
なんかもしあれだったらいいかもしれないといい今すっごいアマート a 私はレバー買っていてもめっちゃ気になるか見てみようかなとすぐリアルタイムで申し訳ないんだけどマイリストに入れました嬉しいガチでマイリストに入れました
I'm so glad I put it on my list.
I'm so glad I put it on my list!
I'll watch it when I have time.
I'll watch it when I have time
I'm afraid not to watch it at night.
I don't think I'll watch it at night.
It's better to see it in the light.
I'll watch it when it's light.
If it's not your thing.
I'm still not good at horror.
I'm sorry, I'm just telling you a scary story.
It's about time for a story like this.
I wonder if it will come, I wonder if it will come, I wonder if it won't come, I wonder if it won't come, I overslept, I'm asking for help, it happens a lot
If it's okay, just for 5 minutes, look, I'll be there, I'll go early, I'm scared